<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science Portfolio on Jordan Kevin Buwa Mbouobda</title>
    <link>https://dataprofessor.github.io/Ken_Portfolio_2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science Portfolio on Jordan Kevin Buwa Mbouobda</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dataprofessor.github.io/Ken_Portfolio_2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deep Transfer Learning for Classification of Breast Cancer</title>
      <link>https://dataprofessor.github.io/Ken_Portfolio_2/post/dtl_breast_cancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dataprofessor.github.io/Ken_Portfolio_2/post/dtl_breast_cancer/</guid>
      <description>Deep Transfer Learning for Classification of Breast Cancer By Jordan Kevin Buwa Mbouobda Supervision: Dr. Prudence Djagba Introduction Deep transfer learning is a machine learning technique that leverages knowledge from one task to improve the performance on a different but related task. In the context of breast cancer classification, algorithms are used to distinguish between cancerous and non-cancerous tumors in medical images such as mammograms.
According to a study conducted by Hyuna Sung, Jacques Ferlay, and other scholars in 2020, there were 19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning algorithms</title>
      <link>https://dataprofessor.github.io/Ken_Portfolio_2/post/real_world_mcmodels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dataprofessor.github.io/Ken_Portfolio_2/post/real_world_mcmodels/</guid>
      <description>Real-world examples of various types of Markov Chain models in Machine Learning By Jordan Kevin Buwa Mbouobda Supervision: Dr. Chris Wood Introduction Markov Chains are powerful models that can capture sequential dependencies in data. They have a wide range of applications in various fields, including Machine Learning. In this presentation, we will explore some real-world examples of Markov Chain models in Machine Learning.
Markov Decision Process To understand the Markov decision process, let&amp;rsquo;s consider you&amp;rsquo;re playing with a die.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://dataprofessor.github.io/Ken_Portfolio_2/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dataprofessor.github.io/Ken_Portfolio_2/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on these social media platforms.
Platform URL Twitter: https://twitter.com/Jordanbuwa LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jordan-buwa-163762257/ GitHub: https://github.com/Jordan-buwa/planets facebook: https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100009344173357 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
